=Reincarnated Love=
=Episode 14=
(If Lu Huaijin)
(is the mastermind behind all this,)
(what will he do next?)
What are you doing?
Yuan,
may peace follow you year after year
with joy by your side.
I've never told you about my birthday.
How did you find out?
I'm Huo Linchuan, after all.
Is there anything I can't discover?
ظآزThe dream shatteredظآز
ظآزLike illusion, yet trueظآز
ظآزLike a restless soulظآز
ظآزHow vagueظآز
ظآزRain and blood, drifting wildظآز
ظآزA blade of frost in dreamsظآز
ظآزLove and hate entwinedظآز
ظآزRise and fall, yet never fadeظآز
Yuan,
the past misunderstandings
ظآزWhen fate falls apartظآز
have all faded like smoke and clouds.
Today is your birthday.
I swear here and now:
For all the remaining years,
I'll do everything to keep you safe
and never abandon you.
If I break my word...
No need for oaths.
ظآزStill, I refuse to bow or yieldظآز
ظآزIn this life, love becomes my bladeظآز
ظآزTo break free from reincarnationظآز
Thank you,
honey.
ظآزIs this fate or calamityظآز
Happy birthday,
dear.
ظآزI ask only for a moment of peace,
as devout as my heartظآز
ظآزIn the next life, grant me one kissظآز
ظآزTo kiss the snow upon the brows,
and the depths of your gazeظآز
ظآزFor once we kissed,
destiny bound us to never partظآز
ظآزThis fleeting life feels but a dreamظآز
ظآزSober or indulgeظآز
By the way,
I have something to show you.
What is it?
What's this?
This armor is called SilverScales.
It followed my ancestors
through hundreds of battles,
protecting its master.
It's a treasured heirloom
of the Huo clan.
Today,
I wish to give it to you.
This...
This armor is so precious.
It's also your family heirloom.
I...
You are the mistress of the Huo clan.
And you are my wife.
This armor protects
the future matriarch of the Huo clan.
But above all,
you are Jiang Ruoli.
You are the very heart of my life.
If one day,
trouble should befall me,
let this armor keep you safe.
ظآزWhere shall I seekظآز
ظآزThe traces of your past livesظآز
ظآزI'd spend a lifetime's luck
just for youظآز
ظآزGazing at your figure
for the rest of my lifeظآز
ظآزUntil time grows us oldظآز
ظآزDreams lift the night
where stars grow thinظآز
ظآزWhen shall I meet you again
in another lifeظآز
ظآزThe galaxy stirs;
destiny endlessly returnsظآز
ظآزIf I could, let me guard you this timeظآز
ظآزHow did this feeling beginظآز
ظآزIn each trial, longing deepensظآز
ظآزAcross vast lands, it still shinesظآز
ظآزWhen the night fades,
the moon shines longerظآز
ظآزA fleeting dream
shines through the rainظآز
ظآزThrough three lifetimes,
we never partظآز
ظآزA thousand years of snow
fall into your palmظآز
ظآزHow does love fade awayظآز
ظآزEach thought recalls the pastظآز
ظآزLonging burns into a lasting acheظآز
ظآزFrost stains the white robesظآز
ظآزMist and clouds veil the skyظآز
ظآزMy past was filled with you aloneظآز
ظآزAll our joy and sorrow shapedظآز
ظآزOur loveظآز
ظآزThe dream shatteredظآز
ظآزLike illusion, yet trueظآز
ظآزLike a restless soulظآز
ظآزHow vagueظآز
ظآزRain and blood, drifting wildظآز
ظآزA blade of frost in dreamsظآز
ظآزLove and hate entwinedظآز
ظآزRise and fall, yet never fadeظآز
ظآزHow can I turn the tides
of this fleeting lifeظآز
ظآزWhen fate falls apartظآز
ظآزMemories return,
carving tears upon my faceظآز
ظآزYet I can't hold onظآز
ظآزOnly warmth remains
where longing once burnedظآز
ظآزLife after lifeظآز
ظآزFated to meet, but never meant to beظآز
ظآزStill, I refuse to bow or yieldظآز
ظآزIn this life, love becomes my bladeظآز
ظآزTo break free from reincarnationظآز
ظآزAll past affairs tangled with regretظآز
ظآزNow shatter apartظآز
ظآزBy fate and karmic ties confinedظآز
ظآزIs this fate or calamityظآز
ظآزIs it life, death, or parting painظآز
ظآزI ask only for a moment of peace,
as devout as my heartظآز
ظآزIn the next life, grant me one kissظآز
ظآزTo kiss the snow upon the brows,
and the depths of your gazeظآز
ظآزFor once we kissed,
destiny bound us to never partظآز
ظآزThis fleeting life feels but a dreamظآز
ظآزSober or indulgeظآز
ظآزI only wish to be with you,
with all my heartظآز